Time,Text,Hashtages,Coordinates,City,Entities,indexes,Person_Name
12:14:10,"as we recognise concern have now move into the 'delay phase' in the uk regard the coronavirus, we would like",[],"[-3.148037, 50.98599]",Taunton,"[['uk', 'GPE'], ['coronavirus', 'ORG']]",57,Superjuicego
12:15:14,everyone: coronavirus will be wipe out once it becomes summer again coronavirus in november 2020:,[],"[-6.546814, 53.178753]",South Dublin,"[['coronavirus', 'ORG'], ['summer', 'DATE'], ['coronavirus', 'ORG'], ['november 2020', 'DATE']]",266,WeWantOleOut
12:15:49,the joy or coronavirus be instead of work today (job get binned) i get to spend time reading through a very deta,[],"[-0.514092, 51.72224]",Hemel Hempstead,"[['coronavirus', 'ORG'], ['today', 'DATE']]",387,chrishughesfilm
12:15:52,"talksport. coronavirus be huge story now. with his take on it, we have on the line john hartson. fucking hell.",[],"[-1.706057, 53.736369]",Leeds,"[['coronavirus', 'ORG'], ['john hartson', 'PERSON']]",401,DarrylKnee
12:16:05,coronavirus be announce a a pandemic yet the only time scottish people take it seriously be when the old firm i,[],"[-3.328512, 55.894729]",Edinburgh,"[['coronavirus', 'ORG'], ['pandemic', 'ORG'], ['scottish', 'NORP']]",450,amygarrodxx
12:17:01,international break still bad than a coronavirus break -,[],"[-2.142873, 51.861864]",Cheltenham,"[['coronavirus', 'ORG']]",625,MichaelWilkie77
12:17:32,coronavirus wont stop me support my team,[],"[-1.957296, 50.574606]",South East,"[['coronavirus', 'ORG']]",742,lewcifer93
12:17:35,s&amp;p500 one year prior to the outbreak of h1n1 and of coronavirus i know there be a wish for exploit the politic,[],"[-0.080028, 51.48432]",Poplar,"[['one year', 'DATE'], ['h1n1', 'GPE'], ['coronavirus', 'ORG']]",750,S_Valdivieso
12:18:42,coronavirus,[],"[-0.18576, 51.604519]",Enfield,"[['coronavirus', 'ORG']]",959,chrispice_musik
12:21:03,right seriously this coronavirus really need to stop now !! i have ticket to see in glasgow in ma,[],"[-4.393285, 55.796184]",Glasgow,"[['coronavirus', 'ORG'], ['glasgow', 'GPE'], ['ma', 'GPE']]",1425,Louise_Sharp1
12:21:58,coronavirus beef in the common,[],"[-0.15191, 51.410792]",Lambeth,"[['coronavirus', 'ORG']]",1606,93_smithereens
12:22:20,i really hope the coronavirus stay away from you the resident and your collea,[],"[-3.30809, 51.387271]",Barry,"[['coronavirus', 'ORG']]",1685,reddevil1975
12:22:42,coronavirus,[],"[-0.292579, 51.555179]",Barnet,"[['coronavirus', 'ORG']]",1775,Mazipita
12:23:28,coronavirus (covid-19). don't ignore it. don't live in fear. take precaution. it be a challenge to humanity which,[],"[-0.074547, 51.414087]",Lewisham,"[['coronavirus', 'ORG']]",1939,OrdrsUK
12:23:38,"so we're go to be just get over the peak of coronavirus and just start to recover then boom,",[],"[-0.667426, 52.333067]",Finedon,"[['coronavirus', 'ORG']]",1977,Joe_Example
12:23:53,in light of the coronavirus i will be take absolutely no time off work and go about my day a normal . working,[],"[-1.289608, 51.712267]",Oxford,"[['coronavirus', 'ORG']]",2025,Njdecorating
12:25:43,fs this coronavirus be get serious. public go nut in the shop for stuff they dont need. it's that bad at m,[],"[-4.481062, 55.813404]",Paisley,"[['coronavirus', 'ORG']]",2363,BBRaymie
12:26:13,"really disappointed to have a 2nd rj conference cancel due to the coronavirus, but totally respect and appreciat",[],"[-2.812244, 53.708601]",Longton,"[['2nd', 'ORDINAL'], ['coronavirus', 'ORG']]",2456,claire54062259
12:26:22,coronavirus now at everton but rumour that jordan pickford have it be completely untrue a he cannot catch anything,[],"[-3.062965, 53.585124]",Southport,"[['coronavirus', 'ORG'], ['everton', 'GPE'], ['jordan pickford', 'PERSON']]",2484,athole52
12:27:29,coronavirus be this the begin of the zombie apocalypse??,[],"[-1.698742, 52.768507]",Burton upon Trent,"[['coronavirus', 'ORG']]",2749,BigPoppaConsole
12:27:52,coronavirus isn't gonna stop me go to the gym to lose weight,[],"[-0.25981, 51.728695]",Hatfield,"[['coronavirus', 'ORG']]",2826,AmiAFCxo
12:28:30,efl statement: coronavirus update,[],"[-2.829936, 54.020096]",Lancaster,"[['efl', 'ORG'], ['coronavirus', 'ORG']]",2961,JanetAndjan
12:30:40,coronavirus [corvid 19] update. we take safety and welfare seriously at axe heads - axe throwing. we have introduce,[],"[-5.279474, 50.21347]",Redruth,"[['coronavirus', 'ORG'], ['safety and welfare', 'ORG'], ['axe heads - axe throwing', 'ORG']]",3364,Axe_Heads
12:32:37,who do you think have the right strategy now to tackle coronavirus?,"['Covid_19', 'COVID_19uk', 'COVID2019IRELAND']","[-6.475708, 53.350862]",Fingal,"[['coronavirus', 'ORG']]",3771,Andy_Kavanagh
12:33:19,coronavirus cant survive in heat 26-27degrees + ... ok who want to fly out to a hot country with me?,[],"[-0.976638, 53.070958]",Southwell,"[['coronavirus', 'ORG'], ['26', 'CARDINAL']]",3922,GanjiKimiya
12:34:29,"if you think this coronavirus be a joke, trust me it not. everyone should and be safe.. it scary out there",[],"[-0.504965, 51.861227]",Luton,"[['coronavirus', 'ORG']]",4150,Ms_Simieyscott
12:35:30,coronavirus: premier league and efl suspend until 3 april at early - well at least this will give my injured,[],"[-0.173706, 50.80835]",Brighton,"[['coronavirus', 'ORG'], ['premier league', 'ORG'], ['efl', 'ORG'], ['3 april', 'DATE']]",4346,TommyCoyneBN1
12:35:50,people that play stuff out loud on the bus be the one who should be get coronavirus. absolute worstcunt behaviour,[],"[-4.393285, 55.796184]",Glasgow,"[['coronavirus', 'ORG']]",4414,AMc88_
12:36:40,petition: include self-employed in statutory sick pay during coronavirus,[],"[-3.07949, 55.928162]",Musselburgh,"[['coronavirus', 'ORG']]",4576,ladystardust31
12:36:43,petition: include self-employed in statutory sick pay during coronavirus,[],"[-4.274143, 57.447943]",Inverness,"[['coronavirus', 'ORG']]",4588,suzlaidlaw
12:37:09,"africa: ""we haven't get coronavirus cuz god like us"" god:",[],"[-2.319934, 53.343623]",Manchester,"[['coronavirus', 'ORG']]",4675,iam_ROMVN
12:38:42,"its not true that the canadian prime minister have coronavirus, but his wife? thats trudeau.",[],"[-1.101931, 53.489561]",Bessacarr,"[['canadian', 'NORP'], ['coronavirus', 'PERSON'], ['trudeau', 'PERSON']]",5015,cal_baldwin
12:38:50,"hi everyone, unfortunately with the level of attention that coronavirus be receive &amp; the number of event that ha",[],"[-1.597958, 53.966206]",Harrogate,"[['coronavirus', 'ORG']]",5042,GeekPubQuiz
12:39:01,coronavirus,[],"[-3.79733, 55.663492]",Lanark,"[['coronavirus', 'ORG']]",5071,CraigFellows7
12:39:23,if thousand of people die in the uk because of coronavirus ...surely boris can't just wash his hand of any responsibility.,[],"[-0.111476, 51.419425]",Camberwell,"[['if thousand', 'CARDINAL'], ['uk', 'GPE'], ['coronavirus', 'ORG'], ['boris', 'PERSON']]",5139,_MattBrown
12:43:28,petition: include self-employed in statutory sick pay during coronavirus,[],"[-0.147596, 53.52505]",Grimsby,"[['coronavirus', 'ORG']]",5985,LynPaul6
12:43:50,great interview skill yr 6 some great information about how to prevent the spread of coronavirus!,[],"[-0.170246, 51.564585]",Tottenham,"[['yr 6', 'PRODUCT'], ['coronavirus', 'ORG']]",6069,CrowlandPrimary
12:44:03,"coronavirus get u anxious people choke in class when we get to cough, it be already bad before you come man",[],"[-3.278624, 51.447362]",Cardiff,"[['coronavirus', 'ORG']]",6121,arabiandxddy
12:44:55,cruise news update (coronavirus) the full list of cruise line who have suspend operation together with their,[],"[-1.308617, 50.836592]",Locks Heath,"[['cruise news update', 'ORG'], ['coronavirus', 'ORG']]",6285,CruiseshipP
12:47:09,because by april 3rd coronavirus would have die off and well all be back to normal....,[],"[-0.328914, 52.535472]",Peterborough,"[['april 3rd', 'DATE'], ['coronavirus', 'ORG']]",6717,pufc_mark
12:49:06,boris johnson best be in that 60% population of get coronavirus.,[],"[-0.142058, 51.518552]",Islington,"[['boris johnson', 'PERSON'], ['60%', 'PERCENT'], ['coronavirus', 'ORG']]",7116,Unknowem
12:51:04,universities in the uk should shut! this be a combination of me not want to catch coronavirus and just be lazy!,[],"[-3.008791, 53.36489]",Liverpool,"[['uk', 'GPE'], ['coronavirus', 'ORG']]",7484,Dohara93
12:51:06,"please incase you be a lady be scar of go to a makeup studio in view of coronavirus, here be what some mak",[],"[-1.839033, 53.823899]",Cottingley,"[['coronavirus', 'ORG']]",7495,DrOlufunmilayo
12:52:02,coronavirus have cancel tour fuck my life,[],"[-3.008791, 53.36489]",Liverpool,"[['coronavirus', 'ORG']]",7674,_niamhmullen
12:52:11,"in the uk, government policy be to let coronavirus run it course whilst note 60% of the population will get it.",[],"[-3.081207, 51.549936]",Newport,"[['uk', 'GPE'], ['coronavirus', 'ORG'], ['60%', 'PERCENT']]",7706,painesrepublic
12:52:12,i dont well ever see anything like this coronavirus again absolutely mental what carnage it causing.,[],"[-3.207316, 51.41538]",Penarth,"[['coronavirus', 'ORG']]",7710,josh_wats09123
12:53:51,westminster: caritas response to the coronavirus via,[],"[-0.213503, 51.512805]",Camden Town,"[['coronavirus', 'ORG']]",8036,ICN_UK
12:54:40,"while the will become far stretch &amp; severely lack resource to cope with coronavirus, spare a thought f",[],"[-2.784107, 53.341503]",Widnes,"[['coronavirus', 'ORG']]",8190,chariots85
12:55:07,coronavirus survival kit for sale 100,[],"[-3.328512, 55.894729]",Edinburgh,"[['coronavirus', 'ORG'], ['100', 'CARDINAL']]",8269,marcfibigT
12:55:35,coronavirus.,[],"[-0.15191, 51.410792]",Lambeth,"[['coronavirus', 'ORG']]",8355,6aelle
13:00:12,really sorry everyone but due to coronavirus we have have too many boxer and volunteer pull out so have to cancel,[],"[-0.259465, 51.417277]",Wandsworth,"[['coronavirus', 'ORG']]",9265,CarneyCommunity
13:02:56,coronavirus will linger after the pandemic ends. but it wont be a bad.,[],"[-2.564752, 53.301534]",Yorkshire and The Humber,"[['coronavirus', 'ORG']]",9792,infamousgrouser
13:04:10,rest of the world: coronavirus (covid-19) pandemic take a fast-mounting toll on life and the economy britain: a touch of the sniffle,[],"[-1.355293, 51.369958]",Newbury,"[['coronavirus', 'ORG'], ['britain', 'GPE']]",10061,armyangus
13:04:41,coronavirus be even popular than mahama.......,[],"[-0.104501, 51.518605]",Hackney,"[['coronavirus', 'ORG'], ['mahama', 'PERSON']]",10179,NanaAnsah20
13:05:46,coronavirus be a death sentence for palestinians cage in gaza - middle east news -,"['CoronaOutbreak', 'lockdown']","[-5.353407, 51.378778]",Wales,"[['coronavirus', 'ORG'], ['palestinians', 'NORP'], ['gaza -', 'GPE']]",10413,bonetticech13
13:10:04,be aware that govt advice coronavirus base on radical experiment: herd immun,[],"[-0.187894, 51.483718]",London,"[['coronavirus', 'ORG'], ['herd immun', 'PERSON']]",11288,KellanFarshea
13:10:11,they've postponed record store day until june! i hate coronavirus and i hate the government and i hate your govern,[],"[-3.278624, 51.447362]",Cardiff,"[['coronavirus', 'PERSON']]",11327,KulaBeth
13:11:34,this coronavirus well hurry up and hit my work so i can't get 2 month off with full pay.,[],"[-2.682408, 50.923946]",Yeovil,"[['coronavirus', 'ORG'], ['2 month', 'DATE']]",11618,alfiejoe122
13:14:09,coronavirus be somehow make me hate this island even more than i already do,[],"[-2.319934, 53.343623]",Manchester,"[['coronavirus', 'ORG']]",12123,splashmaking
