"[{\"event_name\": \"coronavirus\", \"data\": \"{\\\"Time\\\":{\\\"0\\\":\\\"12:14:56\\\",\\\"1\\\":\\\"12:15:51\\\",\\\"2\\\":\\\"12:15:52\\\",\\\"3\\\":\\\"12:15:59\\\",\\\"4\\\":\\\"12:16:01\\\",\\\"5\\\":\\\"12:18:27\\\",\\\"6\\\":\\\"12:15:14\\\",\\\"7\\\":\\\"12:15:49\\\",\\\"8\\\":\\\"12:15:52\\\",\\\"9\\\":\\\"12:16:05\\\",\\\"10\\\":\\\"12:17:01\\\",\\\"11\\\":\\\"12:17:32\\\",\\\"12\\\":\\\"12:17:35\\\",\\\"13\\\":\\\"12:18:42\\\"},\\\"Text\\\":{\\\"0\\\":\\\"pornhub do more to care for people in these trouble time than the uk government\\\",\\\"1\\\":\\\"i honestly don't know where the uk government expert be come from, there's a lot of other people at th\\\",\\\"2\\\":\\\"yep, a drive through to get tested, far to advanced for this uk government let 'em die policy\\\",\\\"3\\\":\\\"i suspect one downside to the uk approach (which i do believe be rational and science based) maybe that it will now\\\",\\\"4\\\":\\\"uk chief scientist say that get 'herd immunity' 60% will be infected. at a fatality rate of 0.5 to 1% that mean a\\\",\\\"5\\\":\\\"how can they fine scotland? arent they part of the uk?\\\",\\\"6\\\":\\\"everyone: coronavirus will be wipe out once it becomes summer again coronavirus in november 2020:\\\",\\\"7\\\":\\\"the joy or coronavirus be instead of work today (job get binned) i get to spend time reading through a very deta\\\",\\\"8\\\":\\\"talksport. coronavirus be huge story now. with his take on it, we have on the line john hartson. fucking hell.\\\",\\\"9\\\":\\\"coronavirus be announce a a pandemic yet the only time scottish people take it seriously be when the old firm i\\\",\\\"10\\\":\\\"international break still bad than a coronavirus break -\\\",\\\"11\\\":\\\"coronavirus wont stop me support my team\\\",\\\"12\\\":\\\"s&amp;p500 one year prior to the outbreak of h1n1 and of coronavirus i know there be a wish for exploit the politic\\\",\\\"13\\\":\\\"coronavirus\\\"},\\\"Hashtages\\\":{\\\"0\\\":\\\"[]\\\",\\\"1\\\":\\\"[]\\\",\\\"2\\\":\\\"['CoronavirusPandemic']\\\",\\\"3\\\":\\\"[]\\\",\\\"4\\\":\\\"[]\\\",\\\"5\\\":\\\"[]\\\",\\\"6\\\":\\\"[]\\\",\\\"7\\\":\\\"[]\\\",\\\"8\\\":\\\"[]\\\",\\\"9\\\":\\\"[]\\\",\\\"10\\\":\\\"[]\\\",\\\"11\\\":\\\"[]\\\",\\\"12\\\":\\\"[]\\\",\\\"13\\\":\\\"[]\\\"},\\\"Coordinates\\\":{\\\"0\\\":\\\"[-0.403988, 51.55309]\\\",\\\"1\\\":\\\"[-3.008791, 53.36489]\\\",\\\"2\\\":\\\"[-5.353407, 51.378778]\\\",\\\"3\\\":\\\"[-4.393285, 55.796184]\\\",\\\"4\\\":\\\"[-0.387744, 51.349772]\\\",\\\"5\\\":\\\"[-2.627102, 51.772978]\\\",\\\"6\\\":\\\"[-6.546814, 53.178753]\\\",\\\"7\\\":\\\"[-0.514092, 51.72224]\\\",\\\"8\\\":\\\"[-1.706057, 53.736369]\\\",\\\"9\\\":\\\"[-3.328512, 55.894729]\\\",\\\"10\\\":\\\"[-2.142873, 51.861864]\\\",\\\"11\\\":\\\"[-1.957296, 50.574606]\\\",\\\"12\\\":\\\"[-0.080028, 51.48432]\\\",\\\"13\\\":\\\"[-0.18576, 51.604519]\\\"},\\\"City\\\":{\\\"0\\\":\\\"Harrow\\\",\\\"1\\\":\\\"Liverpool\\\",\\\"2\\\":\\\"Wales\\\",\\\"3\\\":\\\"Glasgow\\\",\\\"4\\\":\\\"Esher\\\",\\\"5\\\":\\\"Coleford\\\",\\\"6\\\":\\\"South Dublin\\\",\\\"7\\\":\\\"Hemel Hempstead\\\",\\\"8\\\":\\\"Leeds\\\",\\\"9\\\":\\\"Edinburgh\\\",\\\"10\\\":\\\"Cheltenham\\\",\\\"11\\\":\\\"South East\\\",\\\"12\\\":\\\"Poplar\\\",\\\"13\\\":\\\"Enfield\\\"},\\\"Entities\\\":{\\\"0\\\":\\\"[['uk', 'GPE']]\\\",\\\"1\\\":\\\"[['uk', 'GPE']]\\\",\\\"2\\\":\\\"[['uk', 'GPE']]\\\",\\\"3\\\":\\\"[['uk', 'GPE']]\\\",\\\"4\\\":\\\"[['uk', 'GPE'], ['scientist', 'PERSON'], ['60%', 'PERCENT']]\\\",\\\"5\\\":\\\"[['scotland', 'GPE'], ['uk', 'GPE']]\\\",\\\"6\\\":\\\"[['coronavirus', 'ORG'], ['summer', 'DATE'], ['coronavirus', 'ORG'], ['november 2020', 'DATE']]\\\",\\\"7\\\":\\\"[['coronavirus', 'ORG'], ['today', 'DATE']]\\\",\\\"8\\\":\\\"[['coronavirus', 'ORG'], ['john hartson', 'PERSON']]\\\",\\\"9\\\":\\\"[['coronavirus', 'ORG'], ['pandemic', 'ORG'], ['scottish', 'NORP']]\\\",\\\"10\\\":\\\"[['coronavirus', 'ORG']]\\\",\\\"11\\\":\\\"[['coronavirus', 'ORG']]\\\",\\\"12\\\":\\\"[['one year', 'DATE'], ['h1n1', 'GPE'], ['coronavirus', 'ORG']]\\\",\\\"13\\\":\\\"[['coronavirus', 'ORG']]\\\"},\\\"indexes\\\":{\\\"0\\\":206,\\\"1\\\":395,\\\"2\\\":398,\\\"3\\\":423,\\\"4\\\":430,\\\"5\\\":918,\\\"6\\\":266,\\\"7\\\":387,\\\"8\\\":401,\\\"9\\\":450,\\\"10\\\":625,\\\"11\\\":742,\\\"12\\\":750,\\\"13\\\":959},\\\"Person_Name\\\":{\\\"0\\\":\\\"GetTopliss\\\",\\\"1\\\":\\\"obsidianset\\\",\\\"2\\\":\\\"bonetticech13\\\",\\\"3\\\":\\\"fatshez\\\",\\\"4\\\":\\\"TonyCHILE\\\",\\\"5\\\":\\\"CliveWinward\\\",\\\"6\\\":\\\"WeWantOleOut\\\",\\\"7\\\":\\\"chrishughesfilm\\\",\\\"8\\\":\\\"DarrylKnee\\\",\\\"9\\\":\\\"amygarrodxx\\\",\\\"10\\\":\\\"MichaelWilkie77\\\",\\\"11\\\":\\\"lewcifer93\\\",\\\"12\\\":\\\"S_Valdivieso\\\",\\\"13\\\":\\\"chrispice_musik\\\"}}\"}]"